
export default flashCards = {

    1: {
        front: "konnichiha",
        back: "hello"
    },
    2: {
        front: "otousan",
        back: "father"
    },
    3: {
        front: "okaasan",
        back: "mother"
    },
    4: {
        front: "oyasuminasai",
        back: "good night"
    },
    5: {
        front: "ittadakimasu",
        back: "thank you for the meal (before)"
    },
    6: {
        front: "gochisousamadeshta",
        back: "thank you for the meal (after)"
    },
    7: {
        front: "gaikou",
        back: "diplomacy"
    },
    8: {
        front: "saikin",
        back: "recently"
    },
    9: {
        front: "kinnen",
        back: "recent years"
    },
    10: {
        front: "todokoro",
        back: "example"
    },
    11: {
        front: "tanoshii",
        back: "fun"
    },
    12: {
        front: "omoshiroi",
        back: "interesting"
    },
    13: {
        front: "kirei",
        back: "pretty"
    },
    14: {
        front: "oto",
        back: "sound"
    },
    15: {
        front: "koe",
        back: "voice"
    },
    16: {
        front: "kutsu",
        back: "shoes"
    },
    17: {
        front: "tsukue",
        back: "desk"
    },
    18: {
        front: "naka",
        back: "middle"
    },
    19: {
        front: "ue",
        back: "up"
    },
    20: {
        front: "shita",
        back: "down"
    }

}